Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
First I'll run dat
Run around and shoot them
Brand new sound, yes still survival
Here comes the sound boy, live in this world
Intelligence, strength, and luck are swirling, flow
My swelled mind is candid
One punch to Banner in Savannah
An easy knockout, bam bam bam
One time for your mind, live through this
Around the world
It haunts me, the pain of the past
Around the noble god are borrowed things
When the seed that's sown flowers, whose is it
Live and fire the arrow of faith, more more more
There is no peace where you're going
Come on, stand up, don't give up the fight
Now, yes, this instant, die die die
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Hey, look at that.
（トマオ）おい あれ あいつ…
Huh?
Should we do it?
（トマオ）やるか 俺らで
Yeah. We've found our suits and guns, so...
（コンタ）
ああ　スーツも銃も見つかったしな
Kato... Just shoot me!
（計(けい)）加藤(かとう) 俺を撃て！
Damn it!
（加藤）ちくしょう！
（聖(せい)）なに考えてんのよ！
What are you thinking?!
Kei...
（加藤）計ちゃん ごめん
I'm sorry!
It's all right. But just do it!
（計）いいって… やってくれ
Big Brother?
It stopped. It's not disappearing.
止まったぞ 消えるの
（聖）えっ？
（計）痛(いて)え…
（聖）あっ 本当！
You're right!
（計）アア… 痛え
It hurts!
（聖）知ってたの？
銃で撃てば止まるって
Did you know it would stop if you shot it?
No. I just, kind of, tried it.
（加藤）
いや なんとなく やってみた
You poor thing.
（聖）かわいそうに…
ごめんね 守れなくて
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
It seems that as long as you don't die,
you can still go back to normal.
命さえ落とさなければ
元に戻るらしい
えっ… どういうこと？
What do you mean?
So long as we kill that statue before the
time limit and get back to the room,
あの千手観音を時間内に倒して
もう一度 あの部屋に戻れば―
we'll be returned to normal...
腕がなくなろうと脚がなくなろうと
生きてる者は五体満足で帰れる
Even if we've lost an arm or a leg!
Could that be true?
ホントなの？ それ
Will you stay here and watch him?
（加藤）ここにいて
計ちゃんを見ててくれないか？
There's something I want to try!
１つだけ試してみたいことがある
It hasn't noticed us yet.
（トマオ）気づかないぜ あいつ
（コンタ）バックから いくか
（トマオ）ああ
Should we attack it from behind?
Yeah.
Easy win, huh?
楽勝
（トマオ）おう
Yeah.
My arm! My arm!
（コンタ）腕… 腕が！
（トマオ）お… 俺の手！
My hand!
（コンタ）痛え！ 血が止まんねえ
It won't stop bleeding!
Hospital... We gotta get to a hospital!
（トマオ）
何だよ 俺の手じゃねえじゃん
What the hell? That's not my hand!
Hospital... We gotta get to a hospital!
（コンタ）てめえ 捨てんじゃねえ
What the hell? That's not my hand!
Hey, asshole! Don't just throw it away!
（東郷(とうごう)）フゥ…
That thing blew itself up!
こいつ 勝手に はじけたぜ
（トマオ）
こんままじゃ俺らも死ぬって
We're gonna die if we don't do something!
（コンタ）やべえ！
Holy shit!
We better put them back on, quick!
早く腕つけねえと！
（トマオ）つかねえって！
It ain't goin' back on!
（トマオ・コンタ）ウワッ…
There it is!
あった！
If I have this...
こいつなら…
I'm sorry.
ごめん
（物音）
Muzumuzu umuyuzuyu.
（仏像星人）むずむず うむゆずゆ
Damn it! I don't have time for this!
くそ… 時間ねえっつうのに
Muzuzu umuyu!
（仏像星人）むずず うむゆ！
ウッ… ウワーッ！
So the suit IS broken...
やっぱり壊れて…
Hey,
（聖）ねえ なんで
“エッチさせて”って言ったの？
why did you ask me to have sex with you?
I just, uh...
別に…
ただ ヤラせてくれそうだったから
I thought you'd say yes.
あっ…
（計）それだけ
That's all.
ハァ… 君なら そう言うと思った
I knew you'd say something like that.
What does that mean?
…んだよ
（聖）そういうキャラだもん 君
Well, you look like that kind of guy.
That girl... That one who just got killed...
あの子
（計）えっ？
死んだ子 好きだったんでしょう？
You liked her, didn't you?
It's okay, really.
（聖）いいよ 別に
I'm older. I've gotten to know people better.
私 おねえさんだから
人間できてるし
She told me that you are kind of
on a different level.
あの子 言ってた
君は次元が違うんだってさ
私も
ちょっと違ってると思う　だから…
I think I'm a little different too, so...
Just leave me here! Run!
俺を置いて逃げてくれ！
Hey!
おい！ 俺を置いて逃げろ
Leave me and get outta here!
（聖）本…
（計）はぁ？
There's a book...
Huh?
That I placed an order for.
頼んであるんだ
ミランダ・フォスターの「迷宮」
Miranda Foster's "Labyrinth".
（岸本(きしもと)）
“桜丘(さくらおか)聖さん”っていうんだって
Her name was Sei Sakuraoka.
「迷宮」って本 注文してるみたい
It looked like she had ordered
some book called Labyrinth.
Sei Sakuraoka...
“桜丘聖”“迷宮”…
Labyrinth...
It's supposed to come in next week.
At the bookstore by the train station.
（聖）
来週 届くんだ　駅前の本屋さん
Kei, I don't know what's going to happen to me...
計君
私 どうなるか分からないから―
But if anything does, would you
go get that book for me?
そうなったら
取りに行ってくれないかな？
“万が一”ってやつ
いいでしょう？
If by any chance I...
You know what I mean, right?
Is that okay with you?
（計）お… おい！
Hey...
See, I've been going to kickboxing class.
（聖）私 キックボクシングの
ジム通ってんだよ
I've even been in a few matches, too.
試合もやってるし
（計）ムリだ　バカ
This is nuts. You can't!
If I can kill that thing, then maybe
you'll fall for me a little.
（聖）あいつ倒したら
ちょっとは私にホレるでしょう？
I will protect you!
（聖）守ってあげる！
Let's go!
いくぞ！
No way...
ウソ… 私 勝てる
I'm winning!
Kei! I'm going to win!
計君 私 勝つから！
Let's go pick up that book together, all right?
（聖）本 一緒に取りに行こうね
いける　帰れる！
I can do it! And we can go home!
一緒に…
Together...
We can go home!
帰れるよ！
What...
あれ？
So I'm as good as dead...
俺なんか死人と同じで
殺すまでもないってかよ
Not even worth killing, huh?
It's over.
（計）もうダメだ…
Everyone's dead.
みんな死んだ
We're no match for those things.
あんなヤツ 勝てるわけない
く… くそ！
Damn it!
I can do this...
いける　まだ いける！
I can still do it!
I'm sorry...
すまない…
Kei! Are you alive?!
計ちゃん 生きてんのか？ 計ちゃん
Kei!
計ちゃん！
Kei! Hey, Kei!
おい 計ちゃん！
（殴る音）
Hey! Hey!
おいって… おい！
（殴る音）
Ka...
加藤…
Kato...
Wait for me.
待っててくれ
あいつを倒してくっから
I'm going to go kill the other one!
So please stay alive!
頼む　生きててくれ！ 頼む！
Please!
Kei, you're so cool!
（少年時代の加藤）
計ちゃん まじカッコイイよ
You're cooler than Goku or Kenshiro!
悟空(ごくう)とかケンシロウより
（少年時代の計）はぁ？ 俺が？
Who? Me?
YOU'RE the one who's like Kenshiro, Kato...
（計）ケンシロウは お前だよ 加藤
He didn't make it, either, huh?
あいつもダメだったのか
I'm gonna sleep with this tonight.
（歩(あゆむ)）今日は それと一緒に寝るよ
（加藤）雨の夢見るぞ
Then you'll dream about the rain.
（歩）いいよ それでも！
早く雨降んないかな～！
That's okay.
Now I can't wait for it to rain!
Ayumu...
歩… やっぱ 雨降ったな
It really did rain, after all.
Hold on a second! It's me!
（千手観音：宮藤(みやふじ)の声）
ちょ… ちょっと待ってくれ　僕だ
It's me!
僕だ　宮藤
It's Miyafuji.
They got me before I knew what happened.
いつの間にか やられてて…
多分 あのとき…
I think I got eaten up or something...
侵食か何かされたんだと思う
What's going on?
（加藤）何なんだ？
（宮藤の声）ハハハハッ…
信用できないよな やっぱり
I can't blame you for being suspicious.
怖いかい？ 僕のこと
Are you afraid of me?
C'mon, put your gun down.
銃下ろしてくれよ
Amazing!
（宮藤の声）
すごい！ 気分いい！ 最高だ！
It feels great!
This is the best!
Oh yes! It feels great!
いいぞ　いい気分だ！
何でもできる！ 僕は最強だ
I can do anything! I'm invincible!
You can't beat me.
君は 僕には勝てないよ
By the way, this statue has
something to ask you.
それより 仏像から
聞きたいことがあるんだそうだ
君たちは何なんだ？
なぜ現地の生物なんだ？
What are you people, anyway?
Why do you exist here? Who sent you?
誰に頼まれた？
We never did anything to you.
Now I'm the only one left.
君たちには
何も迷惑かけてなかったのに―
とうとう 僕１人になってしまった
（加藤）あっ…
（宮藤の声）何を言っても無視か
Are you just going to ignore whatever I say?
In that case, it's time for you to go bye-bye.
それじゃ バイバイだ
There are two triggers...
トリガー２つ…
Could one of them be for locking on to a target?
もしかして ひとつは
ロックオンするやつじゃねえのか？
It's no good.
ダメだ　近づけねえ
I can't get closer!
I can't keep on dodging him either!
これ以上 よけきれねえ
You're pretty athletic, aren't you?
（宮藤の声）君は運動神経いいなぁ
あと１時間ぐらい
やってみるかい？
You feel like doing this for, say, another hour?
This is it!
（加藤）今度こそ！
（発射音）
（加藤）やべえ！
Crap!
Good! Good! Good!
（宮藤の声）よし！ よし！ よし！
（宮藤の声）ウワッ！
（宮藤の声）アアッ… く… くそ！
Damn it! What is this?
何だ？ これ　ちくしょう！
Shit!
Hey, wait a second!
おい… ちょっと待って！
これ どうする気だ？
What are you trying to do with this?
Stop it!
（宮藤の声）やめてくれ
僕は宮藤だ　僕を犠牲にするのか？
It's me, Miyafuji!
You're just gonna sacrifice me?!
もう終わりだ！ 上に送ってやる！
It's over!
I'm going to send you... up there!
歩！
Ayumu...
ウ～ン…
Big Brother?
兄ちゃん？
Big Brother...
兄ちゃん ごめん
やっぱ雨降っちゃった
I'm sorry. It really did rain.
この偽善者が！
カッコつけやがって！
You little hypocrite!
Think you're really something, eh?
勝ったと思っているのか？
愚か者め！
You think you've beaten me? You fool!
（モンスター）驚いたろう？
Time to get serious.
（モンスター）本気で いくぞ
Ah, my glasses, my glasses...
メガネ メガネ…
What the hell? You're scared stiff.
（モンスター）何だ？
めちゃくちゃビビってんじゃん
I'm going to send you up there
no matter how many times it takes!
何度でも送ってやる！
加藤…
Ka...
Kato...
Fall! Fall!
倒れろ！ 倒れろ！ 倒れろ！
（殴る音）
Big Brother?
兄ちゃん
Big Brother!
殺す　殺してやる！
I'll kill you!
I'll frickin' kill you!
This is bad...
やべえ… 意識 飛びそうだ
I think I'm going to pass out.
Big Brother... Big Brother...
兄ちゃん… 兄ちゃん！
I have to go back!
（加藤）帰らなきゃ　帰らなきゃ…
Fall! Fall! Fall!
（モンスター）
倒れろ！ 倒れろ！ 倒れろ！
I'll tear you to pieces!
バラバラにしてやる！
Smartass!
君は生意気だ！
I'm going back... I AM going back!
帰る… 絶対に帰る！
I'm gonna beat him, and then
I'm gonna go home!
こいつを倒して 俺は帰る！
That hurt...
…てえな
THAT HURT!
痛えなぁ！
（殴る音）
Don't fuck with me!
ふざけんな！
勝てると思ってんのかよ？ ああ？
You think you can beat me? Huh?
Hey, imagine this:
（モンスター）想像してみろよ
お前の脳も僕に食われるんだ！
I'm going to eat your brains!
何だ？ 俺 何やってんだ？
What the hell? What am I doing?
Is this real?
これ 現実か？
There's no way I can beat him.
勝てるわけねえじゃん
手 いっぱいありすぎなんだよ…
He's got way too many hands...
You're so cool! You really are!
（少年時代の加藤）
すっげえ！ ホントすっげえよ！
How come you never lose, Kei?
計ちゃん
なんで 絶対 負けねえの？
（少年時代の計）お前 どっかで
“負けるかも”って思ってんだよ
Deep down, I bet you're thinking
that you might lose.
そういうヤツは負けんだよ！
Well, guys like that ALWAYS lose!
えっ？ “負けるかも”？
Huh?
I'm thinking I might lose?
はい 終わり！ ハハハハッ…
There we go. You're finished!
What a fool!
バ～カ！
I can go back now.
帰れるぞ！ 生きててくれ 計ちゃん
Please be alive, Kei!
Ayumu, I'm coming home!
歩 帰るからな！
ハッ… 兄ちゃん？
Big Brother?
Ka... to...
加藤…
Please...
（加藤）歩が…
Let Ayumu be strong...
ひとりで強く生きて…
On his own...
And let...
幸せに…
him...
なれますように…
find...
happiness...
It's the beginning of a brand new day
A day filled with hope
Open your heart to happiness
Okay. Hear are
your scores
Open your heart to happiness
Kurono
8 Points
Open your heart to happiness
Kurono
8 Points
Total 46 Points
Only 54 points to go!
Open your heart to happiness
Kurono
8 Points
Total 46 Points
Only 54 points to go!
And look up at the big, blue sky
Listen to the voice on the radio
And fill your lungs
With the fragrant air
Kurono
8 Points
Total 46 Points
Only 54 points to go!
With the fragrant air
みんなを…
Kurono
8 Points
Total 46 Points
Only 54 points to go!
One! Two! Three! Let's go!
Kurono
8 Points
Total 46 Points
Only 54 points to go!
One! Two! Three! Let's go!
Everyone...
みんなを返せー！
Bring everyone back!
Kei...
（加藤）計ちゃん
Kurono...
（岸本）玄野(くろの)君
If we do make it back alive,
you wanna go out with me?
（聖）生きて戻れたらさ
私たち つきあわない？
（計）ウソだろう？
This can't be real.
I'm alone.
ひとりだ… 俺 ひとりになった
I'm... all alone.
We all start out as pure and innocent babes
Even if you taste the bitter fruit,
don't be discouraged, walk straight
I know it's in the past, but the rain still stings
I'm lonely as floating ice
I kiss your thin finger
And remember you crying
Even if this is the end
I won't forget your last kiss
I won't forget
I won't forget his kiss
This can't be real.
（計）ウソだろう？ 誰も いねえよ
No one's here.
ウソだろう？ まただよ
This can't be real!
Not yet!
Give me a break!
おい 冗談じゃねえぞ！
何だよ それ！
What the hell is that?
Goddamn it, quit screwing around with me!
てめえ いいかげんにしろよ！
Next episode,
次回 “二度と言うな！”
"Don't Ever Say That Again!"